Junior Software Engineer

Summary

Motivated full-stack engineer who loves learning in a fast paced environment and the ability to contribute to a team. E-commerce experience and a challenging Turing School education combine to make a better leader and developer with regards to product innovation and user focus.

Skills

Technical

Javascript	••••
CSS	••••
HTML	••••
React	••••
Redux	••000
Node.js	••000
GIT	••000

Professional

Activator	••••
Hustler	••••
Creativity	••••
Organization	••••
Adaptability	••••
Strategic	••••
Communication	••••

Education

Turing School of Software and Design

- Student Advisory Board leader

Indiana University of Indianapolis

- BA Economics
- Kelley School of Business

Experience

Arbor Anglers

2019 - Present

Assistant Manager

 Sales focused, but jack of all trades. Currently developing an ecommerce store and branding strategies.

Fly Lords

2018 - Present

Travel Photographer

- Destination Photographer for ad campaigns with major brands in the fly fishing and outdoors industries
- Attract and land new clients through both digital networking and industry events

The Loki Project

2017 - Present

Web Administrator and Customer Support

- Design and manage wordpress and shopify ecommerce platforms
- Developed our best selling product (Lightroom Presets) and handled all customer support

Projects

jessepackwood.com/projects

Coin Watch React, Redux, Firebase, SCSS

https://github.com/jessepackwood/CoinWatch

Cryptocurrency tracking web app that pulls the coincap.io api to watch specific coin performance and track the value of a user generated portfolio. The data is stored in Google Firebase and stored in the front end with Redux.

Movie Tracker React, Redux, Postgres, SCSS

https://github.com/katiescruggs/movie-tracker-frontend

Web app utilizing the movieDB api to pull the most recently released films so a user can sign in and favorite films to their personal account. User accounts are stored in PostgreSQL.

SWApibox Agency React, Jest

https://github.com/jessepackwood/ swapiBox Star Wars api is used to render data about the movies series characters, vehicles, and planets.